Masami Stonebridge

Junior Developer & Graphic Designer



Professional Profile

I am enthusiastic and diligent about creative work. I have a passion in web and mobile application development and am now ready to utilise my skills.

Currently, I am in a Software Development course which extends my skills in web, mobile application both front and back end, programming such as game development, the latest project methodology and business concepts. Overall, I achieved an average of 'A' grades for which I studied hard and enjoyed completing. In addition, I have shared my achievements and study journey at several school open days and Future Expo.

I have three years experience in the design industry which complements my Software design skills.

Career Summary

Bisco Japan | Graphic Designer

Tokyo, Japan | Mar 2001 - Jan 2004

- Designing advertisements, magazines, products, leaflets and company stationery.
- · Planning commercials.
- · Including quotes, marketing and sales.

Additional Experience

Kamome Japanese Playgroup | Administrator

Auckland | 2018 - 2020

Kanpai Japanese Restaurant | Waitress

Auckland | Sep 2008 - Mar 2011

Langham Hotel | House Keeping

Auckland | Apr 2006 - Oct 2009

New Zealand Au-Pair Centre | Child Care

Auckland

Contact Detail

021 02399138

1/37 Paunui Street, St Heliers, Auckland

msm-k0304@hotmail.com

Skills

- HTTP
- · CSS
- JavaScript
- Bootstrap
- Python
- C#
- Django
- Express
- MySQL
- MongoDB
- Illustrator
- Photoshop
- Figma
- Git
- Godot
- Xamarin
- React

Languages

- English
- Japanese

Interests

- Volleyball
- Baking
- Skiing
- Drawing
- Reading
- Ukulele

Education

Diploma in Software Development (NZQA Level6)

Whitecliffe | Auckland | Feb 2022 - Dec 2022

This program covers a wide area of knowledge in application development, web, mobile and game development. Some of these lectures are interacting with other students in agile project teams representing multiple roles such as scrum master, tester, BA and finance.

Diploma in Web Development and Design (NZQA Level 5)

Whitecliffe | Auckland | Jun 2021 - Dec 2021

This diploma course builds skills for the entire web development process using a content management system as the back end including testing and business analysis perspective.

Certificate in Information Technology (NZQA Level 5)

Whitecliffe | Auckland | Feb 2021 - Jun 2021

This program is designed to introduce the role of information technology, introducing the concept of hardware, software, programming with practical tasks to achieve a solid foundation.

Web Design and Programming Course

Multimedia School Wave | Tokyo, Japan

Three-month course to achieve fundamental front-end skills for web design and development with HTML, CSS and JavaScript

Visual Art Design Course

Mac Design Academy | Tokyo, Japan

A one-year course that focuses on visual art software skills on Mac. Such as Illustrator, Photoshop, Shade and QuarkXPress.

Associate Degree in Graphic Design

Joshibi Junior College of Art and Design | Tokyo, Japan

A two-year course for achieving visual expression and communication with design knowledge.

Certificate in English for Academic Study

Auckland University of Technology | Auckland

Certificate in English Language

Auckland University of Technology | Auckland

English For Hospitality (NZQA Level 3)

NZMA / FERN English Academy | Auckland